Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Curator Files, 1979 - 2007
  - Emerging Curators Series: An Artist Who Does Not Speak English Is No Artist - Jakup Ferri, May 16, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Local Transit: Catalogue Materials, May 16, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Echoplex - Mark Hamilton "Road to Ruin" Installation Guide, September 14, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Recent Paintings - Jordan Kanter: Catalogue Correspondence, Draft, September 14, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - In the Poem About Love You Don't Write the Word Love: Administrative, November 16, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition List 2006 - 2007 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress: Hunter Reynold's The Memorial Book, March 30, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Photographic Materials, 1973 - 2002
  - JB Cobb, Martha Edelheit, Ree Morton Exhibition Opening Photographs, October 6, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Jonathan Borofsky "Counting From 1 to 2,048,775" Photographs, November 3, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Juan Downey "Las Meninas" Photograph by Harry Shunk [with note], December 3, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Charles Simonds: A Decade of New Art "Ritual Garden" Photograph, December 7, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - "Idea Warehouse Your Scene-My Scene Boredom-Tension-Suprise, Robin Winters" Photograph by Lizbeth Marano, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Jack Goldstein's "A Ballet Shoe" Photograph, [1975] (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Slide Marathon UAF Showing Photograph, April 8, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - [Unidentified Event Photographs], 1976 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - [Audio Works Photographs], January 1977 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Lencek, Baron, Gifford: Gallery Photograph, March 1977 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Performance Series Contact Sheet: Cindy Sherman, Judy Pfaff, Auction, 1977 - 1978 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - "Pictures" Opening Photographs, September 24, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Auction Negatives, Stuart Sherman Contact Sheet and Negatives, September - December 1978 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Eric Bogosian "Garden" Contact Sheet, November 2, 1978 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - "Artists Magazines IEP" Photograph by Anne Turyn, 1979 - 1980 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - Camille Billops, Hatch-Billops Collection Photographs, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - "Fun at Artists Space," "Try Out for Cover Advertisement" Contact Sheet, Negatives, Photographs, Spring 1979 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - Guy de Cointet "Tell Me" Performance Photograph, August 23, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - Sixth Anniversary Benefit Party at The Mudd Club: Contact Sheets, Invitation, Photographs, October 25, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - Group Exhibition Opening Photographs, November 24, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - 105 Hudson Street: Contact Sheets, Negatives, Slides, Photographs, 1979 - 1980, undated (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - Artists and Models Ball Benefit at Danceteria: Contact Sheets, 1980 (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - Bad Light Photography Show at The Strap: Photographs by Florence Neal, January 1980 (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - Linda Shearer's Welcoming Reception: Contact Sheet, Negatives, Photographs, January 1980 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - Freya Hansell Installation Photograph, January 5, 1980 (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - Photograph of Susan Wyatt, February - March 1980 (Box 119, Folder 35)
  - Exhibition Images, Richard Prince Photograph, February 23, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Jenny Snider "Feet of Fred" Photograph, February 23, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Silvia Kolbowski "Original Photo Used for Announcement Card", February 23, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - "Eggs On End: Standing On Ceremony" Spring Equinox Celebration Photograph, March 20, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - 7 Toronto Artists: Paul Campbell Photograph, April 5, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Reese Williams Announcement Negatives, Photograph, May 17, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - [Unidentified Event Photograph], September 1980 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Frances Hynes/EMF "New York Artists-Diverse Trends" Contact Sheet, December 1, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Architecture: Sequences - Lorna McNeur Photograph, January 17, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Tom Rubnitz Photograph, Slide, January 17, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - "Fun At Artists Space" Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photographs, Spring 1981 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Adrian Piper "It's Just Art" Performance Photograph, April 28, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Andrea Evans, Brad Melamed, Aric Obrosey "Stairway to Suburbia" Photograph for Facades, Landscapes, Interiors, May 29, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Michael Byron "For The Nun" Photograph, May 29, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Selections From The Unaffiliated Artists File Photographs, September 25, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Ken Lum Negatives, November 6, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Robert Carvin with Linda Shearer Photograph, September 25, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Eric Bogosian "Advocate" Photograph, December 8, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Installation Slides, April 9, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Installation, Stephen Whisler: Negatives, April 9, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - 223 West Broadway Images and Photographic Materials, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - "Decade of New Art" Contact Sheet, Photographs by Danuta Otfinowski, May 31, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - "Prior to Memory Jam" Photograph by Paula Court, May 16, 1985 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Selections from the Artists File Photographic Materials, September 21, 1985 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Four Artists: Jenny Snider Photographs, November 2, 1985 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Six Sculptors: Photographic Materials, January 25, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Recent Art from Chicago: Photographic Materials, March 3, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Moderns in Mind: Photographic Materials, April 12, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Artists Space Spring Benefit Photographs, April 22, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Artists Space Benefit at Federal Hall: Contact Sheets by Martha Bergman, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Haui Rashid and Dark Rooms: Negatives, February 5, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Social Spaces: Negatives, January 14, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - "I Miss the Revolution" by Bolek Greczynski and The Crew of the Battlefields Project: Photograph, September 29, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - The AIDS Crisis Is Not Over: Joan Carlomusto "The Holms' Amendment" Photograph, November 17, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Dark Rooms: John Orentlicher Slide, [1989] (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Les LeVeque "Some Questions Concerning Technology" Photograph, March 8, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Beverly Semmes: Photograph, April 19, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Erawa-Era Wars: Ralph Paquin and Ann Stoddard Photographs, April 19, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - "1992 Party at Artists Space Benefit" Photographs, Photocopies (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Putt-Modernism: Slides, August 1, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - 25th Anniversary Book: Photographic Materials, [1997] (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Painting as Paradox: Photographic Materials, November 7, 2002 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Gallery Contact Sheets, Negatives, Photographs, undated (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - "Opening More People Than Art" Negatives, undated (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - "Slides for Lance Kinz", undated (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - [Unidentified Performance Photograph by Nathaniel Tileston], undated (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - [Unidentified Photographic Materials], undated (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Walter Robinson: Art Rite Photographs, Slides, undated (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Artists and Gallery Slides, undated, various (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Ellen Zweig Slides, 1986-1988 (Box 10a, Folder 3)
- Series VIII: Media
  - Subseries A: Sound recordings, video recordings, and films
    Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - "#2", undated; ID: 291.0001 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0001)
      Currrently unavailable until duplication occurs.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements Note
      Original format: TDK EC12 Audio Cassette
    - Alison Knowles, "Onion Skin," "Shoe String," "Silk Threads", undated; ID: 291.0002 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0002, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss.291_0002)
      Original format: Audio Cassette
    - An Te Liu: "Prepared Ground - Final", undated; ID: 291.0003 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0003)
      Original Format: DVD
    - A Place Called Oxmoor: "The Flag of Liberty" by Francis Gomila, 2005; ID: 291.0004 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0004)
      Original Format: DVD-R
    - A Place Called Oxmoor: Correspondence from Francis Gomila, undated; ID: 291.0004a (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0004a)
    - "Artfags! Glory Glory!", undated; ID: 291.0005 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0005)
      Original format: CD-R
    - Artists Committee, October 13, 1986; ID: 291.0006 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0006)
      Original format: JVC Audio Cassette
    - Artists Select III: Chaque Produit, "Trena Noval" (Selected by Carrie Weems), 1991; ID: 128.0007 (Box 128, Media ID: 128.0007)
      Original format: Maxell Audio Cassette
    - Aurelien Froment, "Theatre de Poche", 2007; ID: 291.0008 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0008)
      Original format: DVD
    - "Begin Endless 3/4", undated; ID: 291.0009 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0009)
    - B. George, "Duet", January 19, 1980; ID: 291.0010 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0010)
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
      Original format: Capitol Audio Cassette
    - Body and the Archive: "Showreel" by Emmanuelle Waeckerle, 2001; ID: 291.0011 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0011)
      Original format: VHS
    - Body and the Archive: "Silencio" by Emmanuelle Waeckerle with Andy Coupe, 2003; ID: 291.0012 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0012)
      Original format: CD
    - Bruce Fier, "Mailgram Series", undated; ID: 291.0013 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0013)
    - Bryant McInnis: "Bedford Stuyvesant, Brooklyn Beautiful, Then & Now", Summer 2003; ID: 291.0014 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0014)
    - Bryant McInnis: "Fulton Park Bedford Suyvesant", undated; ID: 291.0015 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0015)
    - Cevdet Erek HDV, August 1, 2009; ID: 291.0016 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0016)
      Original format: Mini DV
    - Close Cassette 1: Guy De Cointet, Ant Farm, Nancy Buchanan, Lauren Klick, undated; ID: 291.0017 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0017)
    - Context and Conceptualism: "Zulu for Medics" by Siemon Allen, 1994; ID: 291.0018 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0018)
    - Corin Sworn, "Atmosphere and Architecture", 2006; ID: 291.0019 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0019)
    - Dan Shipsides, "Pioneers", 2003; ID: 291.0020 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0020)
    - Discoteca Flaming Star: "Sexy Bloody Cat", 2004; ID: 291.0021 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0021)
    - Dominic Alleluia, "Sounds for Dance," "Frog Hollow", 1978; ID: 291.0022 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0022)
      Original format: Sony Audio Cassette
    - "Edgar Mitchell - 6th Man on the Moon," Fia Backstrom (Copy 1), 2001; ID: 291.0023 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0023)
    - "Edgar Mitchell - 6th Man on the Moon," Fia Backstrom [Copy 2], 2001; ID: 291.0024 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0024)
    - Elephant Cemetery: David Maljkovic "Scene for New Heritage" [Copy 1], 2004; ID: 291.0025 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0025)
    - Elephant Cemetery: David Maljkovic "Scene for New Heritage" [Copy 2], 2004; ID: 291.0026 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0026)
    - Empty Space: Sabrina Gschwandtner - Single Channel Works, Installations, 2001 - 2004; ID: 291.0027 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0027)
      Original format: DVD-R
    - eRacism: William Pope.L Installation Documentation, December 2002; ID: 291.0028 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0028)
    - Fatboy Slim "That Patch Says I'll Like (and Don'e Have)", July 2001; ID: 291.0029 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0029)
    - Fernando Doty, "Excerpts from 'Historical Oddity' ", undated; ID: 291.0030 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0030)
      Original format: Ampex Audio Cassette
    - Gertler/Greene, "That's My Side", 2008; ID: 291.0031 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0031)
    - Guy De Cointet, "TSNX CZYVA7ME," "Espanor Ledet Ko Uluner," "A Few Drawings" [Copy 1], undated; ID: 291.0032 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0032)
    - Guy De Cointet, "TSNX CZYVA7ME," "Espanor Ledet Ko Uluner," "A Few Drawings" [Copy 2], undated; ID: 291.0033 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0033)
    - Heidrun Holzfeind, "The Mystery of God Revealed", 2004; ID: 291.0034 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0034)
      Original Format: VHS
    - Helen Levin, "Global Message," "Flea Bag", undated; ID: 291.0035 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0035)
      Original Format: Tracs Audio Cassette
    - Hosok Chung - IPG Application, October 2003; ID: 291.0036 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0036)
    - Hunch and Flail: Christian Rattemeyer, Greg Smith, 2004 - June 2005; ID: 291.0037 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0037)
    - Hunter 1, undated; ID: 291.0038 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0038)
    - Hunter 2, undated; ID: 291.0039 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0039)
    - Hunter 3, undated; ID: 291.0040 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0040)
    - Hunter 4, undated; ID: 291.0041 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0041)
    - Hunter 5, undated; ID: 291.0042 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0042)
    - Hunter 6, undated; ID: 291.0043 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0043)
      An access copy of this material is not available. For more information, please consult a Fales archivist.
      Original Format: CD
    - Hunter 7, undated; ID: 291.0044 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0044)
    - Hunter 8, undated; ID: 291.0045 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0045)
    - Hunter 9, undated; ID: 291.0046 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0046)
    - Hunter 10, undated; ID: 291.0047 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0047)
    - Hunter 11, undated; ID: 291.0048 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0048)
    - Hunter 12, undated; ID: 291.0049 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0049)
    - Hunter 13, undated; ID: 291.0050 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0050)
    - Hunter 14, undated; ID: 291.0051 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0051)
    - Hunter 15, undated; ID: 291.0052 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0052)
    - Hunter 16, undated; ID: 291.0053 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0053)
    - Hunter 17, undated; ID: 291.0054 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0054)
    - Hunter 18, undated; ID: 291.0055 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0055)
    - Ilona Granet, "The Tables Are Turning, " "All Come to Order", undated; ID: 291.0056 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0056)
      Original Format: TDK Audio Cassette
    - International Geographic: S.H. Hermes, Photographed by Alexander Gnaedinger, "Playtime", 2004; ID: 291.0057 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0057)
    - Jacki Apple, "Heart of Palms", 1978; ID: 291.0058 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0058)
    - Jeffrey Campbell, Pianist, undated; ID: 291.0059 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0059)
    - Jeremiah Burnham, "Chronsynclasticinfididibuwm", undated; ID: 291.0060 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0060)
      Original format: Realistic Audio Cassette
    - John Baldessari, "Alfred From Berlin", 1979; ID: 291.0061 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0061)
    - John Baldessari, "Alfred From Berlin" / Michael Smith, undated; ID: 291.0062 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0062)
    - Joseph Nechvatal - NYC, 1978; ID: 291.0063 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0063)
    - Kiosk: Adam Pendleton Presentation, Eyebeam Lab Mag Launch, 2006; ID: 291.0064 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0064)
    - Latoya Frazier, undated; ID: 291.0065 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0065)
    - Lea Lagasse, "Oops!...I Did It Again 11, 23 Loop", undated; ID: 291.0066 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0066)
    - Lee Walton, "Making Changes", November 11, 2004; ID: 291.0067 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0067)
    - Leon Golub, Painter, undated; ID: 291.0068 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0068)
      Original format: Scotch Audio Cassette
    - Lines of Loss: "Ligne D'Abandon" by Manuel Rocha, Gabriel Orozco, 1993; ID: 291.0069 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0069)
    - Lines of Loss: "Under the Green Time" by Roger Doyle, undated; ID: 291.0070 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0070)
    - "Lots O' Prince", undated; ID: 291.0071 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0071)
    - Marisa S. Olson: "The One That Got Away," "MoTV News, Episode 1," "Top 40 (Photo Gallery," "Easy Listening," "moiMovies"), undated; ID: 291.0072 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0072)
    - Mark Orange: "2 Short Films: 'The Collaboration,' 'Rise and Fall' ", 2006; ID: 291.0073 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0073)
    - Mark Orange: "Interview with Fred Fisher", 1998; ID: 291.0074 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0074)
    - Mark Orange: "The Morning After" (Copy 1), 1998; ID: 291.0075 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0075)
    - Mark Orange: "The Morning After" (Copy 2), 1998; ID: 291.0076 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0076)
    - Mark Orange: "Rehearsing 'Ascension' ", 2002; ID: 291.0077 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0077)
    - Mark Orange: "Then", 2002; ID: 291.0078 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0078)
    - Mark Orange: "Toor o Fable" (Copy 1), 1997; ID: 291.0079 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0079)
    - Mark Orange: "Toor o Fable" (Copy 2), 1997; ID: 291.0080 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0080)
    - Martha Rosler, "What's Your Name, Little Girl?", undated; ID: 291.0081 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0081, Box Digitized Access Files, File mss.291_0081)
    - Mary Coble: "Binding Ritual (daily routine)", undated; ID: 291.0082 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0082)
    - Mary Coble: Conner Contemporary Art, undated; ID: 291.0083 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0083)
    - Michael Smith, "It Starts at Home", undated; ID: 291.0084 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0084)
      Original format: TDK AD Audio Cassette
    - Micki McGee, "Her Intestinal Bypass Surgery", undated; ID: 291.0085 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0085)
    - Mike Figgis, "Jeremy Deller's The Battle of Orgreave", 2006; ID: 291.0086 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0086)
    - Mimi Smith, "Color TV News", 1978; ID: 291.0087 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0087)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Catherine Ross, "Fingering and Footing", 2005; ID: 291.0088 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0088)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Chad Nelson Video Work, 2004; ID: 291.0089 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0089)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Diane Derr Disc 1, "Three and a Half," "Via Email", 2004; ID: 291.0090 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0090)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Diane Derr Disc 2, "Tootsie Licks", 2005; ID: 291.0091 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0091)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Iris Bernblum, 2005; ID: 291.0092 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0092)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Iris Bernblum, undated; ID: 291.0093 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0093)
    - The Mind/Body Problem: Ra Di Martino, 2006; ID: 291.0094 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0094)
    - "Mixed Rain" (Empty), May 1983; ID: 291.0095 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0095)
      This is an empty TDK audio cassette case.
    - "Museum of Art + Design", 2008; ID: 291.0096 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0096)
    - "My DVD", undated; ID: 291.0097 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0097)
    - "Myth Labs", 2009; ID: 291.0098 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0098)
    - Nancy O'Connor: "Echoes Series Sound Pieces", 1990; ID: 291.0099 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0099)
      Original format: Maxell XL II-S Audio Cassette
    - "Neue Sichchailshopie", undated; ID: 291.0100 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0100)
    - Painting as Paradox: Sue Hettmansperger, Lawrence Fritts, "Mappaemundi", 2001; ID: 291.0101 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0101)
    - Pictures: Prophecies at The Swiss Institute, January 20, 2000; ID: 291.0102 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0102)
    - Ping Chong: "Plage Concrete", 1988; ID: 291.0103 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0103)
    - Pomeroy, "Four Pieces", 1979; ID: 291.0104 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0104)
      Original format: TDK D-C30 Audio Cassette
    - Poppy Johnson, "Untitled", March 1973; ID: 291.0105 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0105)
      Original format: Memorex Audio Cassette
    - Purloined: "Free Massage Phase II" by Nancy Hwang, 1996; ID: 291.0106 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0106)
    - Repeat Performance: Jill Miller, "Single-Channel Videos", 2001 - 2003; ID: 291.0107 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0107)
    - Repeat Performance: Jill Miller, "Single-Channel Videos" Descriptions, 2001 - 2003 (Box 128, Folder ID: 291.0107a)
    - Reynold Weidenaar Works, 1976 - 1979; ID: 291.0108 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0108)
      Original format: TDK SA-C90 Audio Cassette
    - Robert Arndt: "Lines for the Next Exhibition", 2003; ID: 291.0109 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0109)
    - Robert Peters, "Perfection: The Birdiest Bird", 1987; ID: 291.0110 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0110)
    - Ronnie Bass, "Our Land", undated; ID: 291.0111 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0111)
    - "Routines, Long Version", undated; ID: 291.0112 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0112)
    - Salon: "Bridge To Infinity - The Vision of Ursula Hodel", 1993; ID: 291.0113 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0113)
    - "Sleep in a Nest of Flames: A Portrait of a Poet - A Portrait of a Century", 2000; ID: 291.0114 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0114)
    - Simply Because You're Near Me: Jennie C. Jones, 2003; ID: 291.0115 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0115)
      Original Format: CD-R
    - "Swamp, 1971" Nancy Holt, Robert Smithson, undated; ID: 291.0116 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0116)
    - T.B.O.L. "First Ambition," Close to Death "She's An Heiress", 2001; ID: 291.0117 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0117)
    - Teaching TV: Screening + Panel Discussion (Tape 1), November 9, 1990; ID: 291.0118 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0118)
      Original format: Sony HF Audio Cassette
    - Teaching TV: Screening + Panel Discussion (Tape 2), November 9, 1990; ID: 291.0119 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0119)
    - "The Critics Voices IV": Marshall Epron, Marvin Heiferman, Gary Indiana, Paul McMahon, Jeff Perrone, May 16, 1986; ID: 291.0120 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0120)
      Original format: Maxell XL II Audio Cassette
    - "Triumph I + II" (Copy 1), undated; ID: 291.0121 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0121)
    - "Triumph I + II" (Copy 2), undated; ID: 291.0122 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0122)
    - Unidentified Audio Cassette, undated; ID: 291.0123 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0123)
      Original format: TDK Audio Cassette
    - Urban Pornography: Warren Neidich Video Sample, 2001; ID: 291.0124 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0124)
    - "Victor Henderson Takes a Walk", November 2 - 12, 1978; ID: 291.0125 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0125)
    - Vito Acconci, "Now do you Believe the Dirty Dogs are Dead," "Monument to the Dead Children," "Decoy for Birds and People", 1978, 1979; ID: 291.0126 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0126)
      Original Format: Maxell UD XLII Audio Cassette
    - Walter Frederick Bauer, "Wichita Vortex Sutra", December 18, 1985; ID: 291.0127 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0127)
    - Weiner / Landry, "Having Been Built on Sand With Another Base (Basis) in Fact", undated; ID: 291.0128 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0128)
      Original format: Superex Audio Cassette
    - WIlliam Wegman, "History of the World", undated; ID: 291.0129 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0129)
    - Zaha Hadid: Showreel, May 29, 2003; ID: 291.0130 (Box 128, Media ID: 291.0130)
  - Subseries B: Data Storage
    Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - 3rd Berlin Biennial for Contemporary Art: Press, February 2004 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0001)
    - 15th Anniversary Catalogue, undated (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0002)
      Original Format: Maxell MD2-D 5" Floppy Disk
      Capacity: Unknown
    - [15th Anniversary] Master List, March 23, 1989 (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0003)
    - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: Table of Contents, Title Page..., [1998] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0004)
      Original Format: Imation 3.5" Floppy Disk
      Capacity: 1.40 MB
    - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: Tiffany Files from AFA - Early Competitions [Disk 1], [1998] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0005)
      Original Format: 3.5" Floppy Disk
    - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: Tiffany Files from AFA - Early Competitions [Disk 2], [1998] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0006)
    - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: Tiffany Files from AFA - Early Competitions [Disk 3], [1998] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0007)
    - 5000 Artists Return to Artists Space: Tiffany Files from AFA - Early Competitions [Disk 4], [1998] (Box 129, Disk ID: 291.3.0008)